<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Celeg]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Celeg]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/celeg/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 10:38:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/celeg/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>2003 - 2006 AGFA Developer - Team leader  Within the radiology information systems product team my team was responsible for the reporting and speech modules. Reporting in this sense must be seen as the activities a radiologist performs on a radiological study. In this process the radiologist can be assisted by speech technology. My team was responsible for the analysis and development of new features in that area of the product, the integration with the third party speech API (Philips). I was the team leader of the development team. In that role I took part in the development of the solution, but also coached the other developers and acted as a single point of contact for the stakeholders of our team (testing, helpdesk, and product managers)</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.celeg.be/#resume</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">14678214-8de7-4aaf-8dd4-d573a6e53391</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 10:38:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>EDUCATION 1996 - 2000 VLEKHO Master in Commercial Sciences  Computer Science & Engineering Completed graduation from Vlekho with a minor in Computer Science. Graduated with distinction.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/celeg/education-1996-2000-vlekho-master-in-commercial-sciences/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9798dfa6-2e63-4017-afbd-227c5db44add</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 10:27:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.celeg.be/images/bart_profile.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/celeg/35840f92-817a-455b-8530-c8550d6c4f3a/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">35840f92-817a-455b-8530-c8550d6c4f3a</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 10:27:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>MAY 2013 - APRIL 2014 REALDOLMEN Unit Manager / Scrum coach  In May 2013 I joined RealDolmen as a unit manager of the Microsoft Competence Center. In that role I was responsible for a group of 80 Microsoft consultants. My main activities were competence development, recruitment, resource planning, budgeting and forecasting, (pre)sales.  Next to that I was active as a Scrum coach and trainer. I continued to work for Barco to help them to roll out Scrum in a large division spread over different countries.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/celeg/may-2013-april-2014-realdolmen-unit-manager-scrum-coach/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">51237c77-e2c7-4c94-8f36-0742c4576603</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 10:27:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.celeg.be/images/cinecare.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/celeg/b72f1f40-f265-43ef-bb83-f6603ed56bfe/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b72f1f40-f265-43ef-bb83-f6603ed56bfe</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 10:25:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Working in software development since the year 2000 in a variety of different roles. Ever since the start of my career I have been in software development. I started as a functional analyst without any development background and then moved on to learn how to code in C#. Pretty early already I got bitten by the Agile way of doing projects. The first Agile project I did as a PM / Scrum Master (what's in a name) was back in 2006 and since then I have always been involved in Agile projects. Later on I also started coaching Agile teams that were making the transition from the traditional way of building software. Currently I am working as an Agile PM / CTO for a small startup. That is a pretty broad role. It involves defining the roadmap for the product, helping the team with the planning, but also helping the team with technical architecture choices and even writing some code in PHP.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/celeg/working-in-software-development-since-the-year-2000-in-a-var/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a3d1c3b0-8bef-4c03-90ae-9e8f6329b1fb</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 10:25:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>EMPLOYMENT MAY 2014 - PRESENT TAGTAGCITY Agile PM - CTO  TagTagCity is a small startup that has 2 products: a mobile web site generator (mobiloptim.com) and a native mobile app for municipalities (mobicities.be) In my role as Agile PM and CTO I define the roadmap for the product in collaboration with the company’s board of directors and I plan and follow up the work together with the team. I am also responsible for the technical decisions regarding the product. We use Scrum as a methodology and work in weekly sprints. From a technology perspective we use PHP and the Laravel framework and run both of our products on the Azure cloud.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/celeg/employment-may-2014-present-tagtagcity-agile-pm-cto-tag/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6ab0d716-542a-4ef4-8482-cd6f3899114d</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 10:24:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>